Attendance number 16, Ema Sakurai, from Ebisu City Junior High School, and
Nakamura Yuna, attendance number 17.
Yes, so we have interviewed each other in the previous and previous two issues,
This time, we would like to talk about the future of Ebisu Chugaku.
This time, we would like to talk about the future of Ebichu.
On January 6 and 7, the new year will begin.
New Year's Big Show 2024 at Fear Arena MM
The dragon that flies high and our future will be held at Fear Arena MM on January 6 and 7.
Just a brief description.
What kind of concert will it be?
I have a feeling that it will be a bit of a festive show since it's the New Year.
Also, EBITU has many genres of music,
You can listen to many different kinds of songs at this concert.
I think this concert will be a lot of fun for those who used to like EBITU and for those who have recently come to like EBITU.
I hope you will come and enjoy the show.
We M.YUNA will be performing at Kanda Square Hall on December 5.
Tokyo Night Land Vol. 4
We will be performing in the Shinseigumi Bakumatsu Yoru Mimamitai.
The daytime performance will start at 3:00 p.m. and the nighttime performance will start at 7:00 p.m.
Those performing are Emma Sakurai, Yuna Nakamura, Haruna Sakamoto, and Yuzuki Ohguro,
Kurumi Hori, Rina Yuki, Rina Kitami, Rina,
Tomoko Hazuki, Hao Koichi, and Aoba Mori,
Kane is playing the role of the Kyushu girl.
We are in the middle of rehearsals.
I have a shield,
Yes, that's right.
It's the first time for me to play the shield so properly,
I've never held it properly,
I'm always very excited during rehearsals,
It's a little bit difficult in some parts,It's a little difficult in some areas,
I hope you will enjoy it,
I'm going to do my best to make it enjoyable for you.
I'm going to have a lot of muscle aches and pains, aren't I?
It's the real work of arms.
The first time you do it for the first time, your muscles ache.
That's right. That's why I'm working hard in various places,
I hope everyone will come.
It has already been announced, but let me tell you the name of our roles.
I am Keima Sakurai, who plays the role of Isamu Kondo.
I am Yuna Nakamura, who plays the role of Shizuo Hijikata.
We will do our best under these names, so please come and play with us,
Please come and play with us.
Who are your partners so far?
Ebisu Chugaku's Sakurai Keima and Nakamura Yuna.
Yuna Nakamura of Ebisu Junior High School.
Bye bye!